(Penny:)what would you most regret
not having told someone?"
(Sheldon:)So, it would be today?
(Sheldon:)Huh.
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose there's
something satisfying
(Sheldon:)about dying on my birthday.
(Penny:)Today's your birthday?
(Amy:)Yes.
(Raj:)Well, that's
always been a secret!
Not even Amy knows!
(Sheldon:)Well, I don't enjoy presents.
(Sheldon:)And the thought of people
(Sheldon:)jumping out and yelling
"Surprise!" fills me
(Sheldon:)with more dread than the words
"George Lucas Director's Cut."
(Penny:)So, why did you finally tell me?
(Sheldon:)The point of the experiment is
(Sheldon:)to be completely honest
with each other.
(Penny:)Well, thank you
for sharing it with me.
(Penny:)I won't tell anyone.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Penny:)That is so funny.
(Penny:)I never would have
pegged you for a Pisces.
(Sheldon:)You're making it difficult
to love you right now.
Great news!
Your bag was returned.
Oh, thank God!